http://www.yourlawyer.com/terms-of-use/

Queens Attorneys
Why Trust Us?
Home > Terms Of Use
Welcome to Parker Waichman!
The terms and conditions of use detailed below (the “Terms of Use”) govern your access to and use of yourlawyer.com and any other websites of Parker Waichman LLC (“Parker Waichman,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) (collectively, the “Sites”). They apply to all users visiting the Sites in any way, including use of the services and resources that we make available to you through the Sites and in related interactions, as described below (the “Services”).
By accessing and using the Sites, you agree to comply with and be bound by our Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy then in effect, and by all applicable law. Please review the following terms carefully. If you do not agree with any of the Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Sites for any purpose. We reserve the right to terminate or limit your access for any violation of the Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy, or for any other reason, in our sole discretion.
TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT
Effective Date: May 10, 2020
Material modifications and related effective dates may be accessed by scrolling to the bottom of the page.
PARTIES
These Terms of Use are a legal and binding agreement between you and Parker Waichman. They govern your access to and use of the Sites, as well as any related applications and activities, currently in use or as we may introduce from time to time.
USE
Parker Waichman hereby grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable, limited right and license to access and use the Sites, solely for your personal use, in accordance with these Terms of Use. You shall not, in any way, otherwise copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, modify, create derivative works from, sell, or exploit the Sites.
Parker Waichman may at any time, for any reason, and without notice or liability: (a) modify, suspend, or terminate operation of or access to the Sites and related services, or (b) change, revise, or modify the Sites and affiliated services.
ARBITRATION
With the exception of actions to protect intellectual property rights and to enforce an arbitrator’s decision hereunder, all disputes, controversies, or claims that arise out of, or relating to, this “Terms of Use” agreement or a breach thereof shall be submitted to and finally resolved by arbitration under the rules of the American Arbitration Association (AAA) that are in effect at that time.
One arbitrator shall be chosen by mutual agreement of the parties in accordance with AAA rules. Arbitration shall take place in Florida or New York, USA, and may be conducted in person, by telephone, or online. The arbitrator shall apply the laws of the states of Florida or New York, USA, depending on the location of the involved office, to all issues in dispute. The controversy or claim shall be arbitrated individually and without consolidation in any other arbitration, claim, or controversy involving any other party. The arbitrator’s findings will be final and binding on all parties, and may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction for enforcement. Enforcements of any award or judgment shall be governed by the United Nations Convention on the Recognition and Enforcement of Foreign Arbitral Awards. Should either party file an action contrary to this provision, the other party may recover attorney’s fees and costs up to $1,000.00.
Consumer Rights Information; California Civil Code Section 1789.3. If the Sites charges for services, products, content, or information, such pricing information will be posted as part of the ordering process for the Sites. We also maintain contact information, including an email address for notifications of complaints and for inquiries concerning pricing policies, in accordance with California Civil Code Section 1789.3. All correspondence should be addressed to our agent for notice at the following address. You may contact us with complaints and inquiries regarding pricing. We will investigate and respond to the inquiries.
Notification of Consumer Rights Complaint or Pricing Inquiry:
Parker Waichman LLP
6 Harbor Parker Drive
Port Washington, New York 11050
(516) 466-6500
The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1020 N. Street, #501, Sacramento, CA 95814, or by telephone at 1-916-445-1254.
CONTROLLING LAW
This “Terms of Use” agreement shall be construed under the laws of the states of Florida and New York in the United States of America, excluding rules concerning conflicts of law. The application of the United Nations Convention of Contracts for the International Sale of Goods is expressly excluded.
CONSUMER INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION
Your use of the Services may involve the transmission to us of certain personally identifiable information. Our policies with respect to our collection and use of such information are set forth in our Privacy Policy, which is hereby incorporated by reference in its entirety. You may provide contact information, including: name, address, email, company, phone number, and other related information. You certify, warrant, and represent that the telephone numbers, emails and other contact information you provide are your contact information, and that you are permitted to receive calls and/or text messages at each of the telephone numbers you have provided.
By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you consent to Parker Waichman contacting you at any telephone number or email address associated with your account, or using other electronic means of communication, to the extent permitted by law. This contact may include, but is not limited to, the use of prerecorded/artificial voice messages and/or an automatic telephone dialing or texting system. You agree that any phone calls between you and Parker Waichman or any of our affiliates, agents, case managers, paralegals, and/or attorneys may be recorded. If you do not want to receive such email messages or telephone calls (including at any wireless number you may have voluntarily provided us), please refer to our Privacy Policy to review your options.
By entering into these Terms of Use or using the Parker Waichman Sites, you consent to receiving communications from us, including via e-mail, text message, calls, and push notifications, even if your number is on a do not call list. You agree that texts, calls or prerecorded messages may be generated by automatic telephone dialing systems.
IF YOU WISH TO OPT OUT OF PROMOTIONAL CALLS OR TEXTS, YOU MAY EMAIL PRIVACY@YOURLAWYER.COM OR CALL US AT 1-516-466-6500. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE NOT REQUIRED TO CONSENT TO RECEIVE PROMOTIONAL TEXTS OR CALLS AS A CONDITION OF USING PARKER WAICHMAN SITES OR SERVICES.
DEFAMATION AND DECENCY
The Sites are a provider of “interactive computer services” under the Communications Decency Act, 47 U.S.C. Section 230, and, as such, our liability for defamation and other claims arising out of any postings to the Sites by third parties is limited as described therein. We are not responsible for content or any other information posted to the Sites by third parties. We neither warrant the accuracy of such postings nor exercise any editorial control over such posts, nor do we assume any legal obligation for editorial control of content posted by third parties nor liability in connection with such postings, including any responsibility or liability for investigating or verifying the accuracy of any content or any other information contained in such postings.
COPYRIGHT
We are committed to complying with United States copyright and related laws. Owners of copyrighted works who believe that their rights under United States copyright law have been infringed may take advantage of certain provisions of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the “DMCA”) to report alleged infringements.
The Sites are an Internet “service provider” as described under DMCA, 17 U.S.C. Section 512. The Sites maintains specific contact information, provided below, as mandated by the DMCA, which includes an email address for notifications of claimed infringement concerning materials posted to the Sites. Notices are to be addressed to the contact person specified below, who is our agent for notice of claimed infringement.
Our agent for notice of claimed infringement may be contacted with complaints regarding allegedly infringing posted material; we will investigate all such complaints. Should posted material, deemed in good faith by us to be in violation of applicable laws, such material will be removed or blocked. We will advise the posting party of the action taken.
The DMCA requires you to include the following information when advising us of a violation. Failure to include all of the following information may result in processing delays:
(i) a description of the copyrighted work that is the subject of the claimed infringement;
(ii) a description of the infringing material and information that will enable us to locate the alleged material;
(iii) your contact information (address, telephone number, and/or email address);
(iv) your statement that you, in good faith, believe that the involved material is not authorized by the copyright owner or its agent, or by law;
(v) your statement, signed under penalty of perjury, that the information you provide is accurate and that you have the authority to enforce the copyrights claimed to be infringed; and
(vi) the copyright owner’s—or a person authorized to act on his/her behalf—physical or electronic signature.
NO PROVISION OF MEDICAL ADVICE
The information contained on the Sites is general information, provided for educational and informational purposes only. Nothing on the Sites is medical advice, nor intended as a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Nothing on the Sites should supplement or inform in any way your medical decisions or a decision to seek medical advice. Always consult a physician for diagnosis and treatment of any medical condition or for any questions you may have regarding a health concern. Never disregard professional medical advice, alter a prescription plan in anyway, or delay or refrain from seeking medical advice because of something you have read or seen on the Sites. Do not make any make decisions regarding medication or medical providers based on information from the Sites.
NO CREATION OF ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP
Information contained on or made available through the Sites is not intended to and does not constitute legal advice, recommendations, mediation or counseling under any circumstance. Nothing on the Sites is an offer to perform services. The content and features on the Sites do not create, and are not intended to create, an attorney-client relationship. Parker Waichman EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY WITH RESPECT TO ACTIONS TAKEN OR NOT TAKEN BY YOU BASED UPON ANY INFORMATION OR OTHER CONTENTS OF THIS SITE. You should not rely on any opinion except that of an attorney you have retained, who has a professional duty to advise you after being fully informed of all the pertinent facts, and who is licensed in the applicable state, and is familiar with the applicable law.
Only individuals who have entered into a mutually signed retainer agreement with Parker Waichman are Parker Waichman clients. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN ASKING US TO REPRESENT YOU, PLEASE CAL OR EMAIL US SO WE CAN DETERMINE WHETHER THE MATTER IS ONE FOR WHICH WE ARE WILLING OR ABLE TO ACCEPT PROFESSIONAL RESPONSIBILITY.
FORCE MAJEURE
We will not be liable for damages involving any delay or failure of delivery arising out of causes beyond our reasonable control and without our fault or negligence. This includes, but is not limited to, acts of God, acts of civil or military authority, fires, riots, wars, embargoes, Internet disruptions, hacker attacks, or communications failures.
INTENDED FOR USE ONLY WITHIN THE UNITED STATES
The Sites are controlled, operated, and administered by Parker Waichman from offices within the United States and are only intended for use within the United States. We do not represent that the Sites are appropriate for use elsewhere. Access to the Sites from locations where its contents are illegal is not authorized.
JURISDICTION AND VENUE
The courts of Nassau, Suffolk, and Manhattan counties in the State of New York and the courts of Lee County in the State of Florida, USA shall be the exclusive jurisdiction and venue for all legal proceedings not arbitrated under these “Terms of Use.”
OWNERSHIP
The Sites and Parker Waichman software, systems, technology, and know-how are owned by or licensed to Parker Waichman and are protected by copyright, trademark, trade dress, patent, and/or other intellectual property rights and proprietary rights. All trademarks, trade names, graphics, logos, and trade dress included in or made available through the Sites and Online Services are owned by or licensed to Parker Waichman and protected by U.S. and international trademark laws (collectively, the “Marks”).
Except as expressly set forth herein, nothing herein shall be construed to confer any grant or license of any Parker Waichman Intellectual Property Rights, whether by estoppel, by implication, or otherwise. You are strictly prohibited from using any Parker Waichman intellectual property except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use. You are also advised that Parker Waichman and its licensors will aggressively enforce its intellectual property rights to the fullest extent of the law.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
IN NO EVENT SHALL THIS SITE AND/OR ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO ANYONE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY TYPE OR KIND. THIS INCLUDES LOSS OF DATA, REVENUE, PROFITS, USE, OR OTHER ECONOMIC ADVANTAGE ARISING OUT OF, OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THIS SITE, ITS PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND/OR CONTENT, ANY INTERRUPTION, INACCURACY, ERROR, OR OMISSION, REGARDLESS OF CAUSE, EVEN IF THIS SITE OR OUR LICENSORS HAVE BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
The Sites contain links to third party web sites for the convenience of our users. Parker Waichman does not endorse these third party sites and does not imply any association between Parker Waichman and those sites. We do not review or control third-party websites that link to or from the Sites and cannot represent that their policies and practices will be consistent with these Terms of Use. We are not responsible for the content of these third-party sites, and we do not represent that such content is accurate or appropriate. Your use of any third-party site is on your own initiative, at your own risk, and potentially subject to the other sites’ terms of use and privacy policy.
LINKS TO THIS SITE
We grant to you a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the Sites provided that the link does not portray us or our products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or offensive way. You may not use any logo, trademark, or trade name, or other proprietary graphic image that may be displayed on the Sites in the link without our prior written consent.
MODIFICATIONS
We reserve the right to modify these “Terms of Use” at any time, and without prior notice. We will make our modifications known by posting an amended “Terms of Use.” The “Terms of Use,” including amendments, are available by link on the homepage, and should be viewed from time to time to understand material modifications and related effective dates.
READERS’ CONTINUED USE OF THIS SITE FOLLOWING OUR POSTING OF A MODIFICATION NOTICE/NEW “TERMS OF USE” CONSTITUTES BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THOSE MODIFICATIONS/NEW “TERMS OF USE.”
MONITORING
We reserve the right, but not the obligation, to monitor your access and use of the Sites without notification to you. We may record or log your use in a manner as set out in our Privacy Policy that is accessible though the Privacy Policy link on the Sites’s home page.
Onward Transfer of Personal Information Outside Your Country of Residence Any personal information we may collect on the Sites will be stored and processed in our servers, which are only located in the United States. If you reside outside of the United States, you consent to the transfer of personal information outside your country of residence to the United States.
PARTICIPATION IN PROMOTIONS OF ADVERTISERS
You may enter into correspondence with, or participate in, promotions of advertisers that promote their products, services, or content on the Sites. Any such correspondence or participation, including delivery of and the payment for, products, services, or content, are solely between you and each such advertiser.
SUBMISSIONS AND POSTINGSBLOGS, FORUMS, CHAT ROOMS, ETC.
You are solely responsible for any information, content, or material you transmit to or through the Sites (“Submissions”). When you post to areas on the Sites that other readers may view, that information is not considered proprietary, private, or confidential. This means that we are under no obligation to monitor posts made to the Sites and are not required to apply editorial control over such posts. We do reserve the right to review such posts and remove material that we deem to be inappropriate. Likewise, posting, transmitting, promoting, using, distributing, or storing content that may subject us to any potential legal liability or that violates applicable laws or regulations, or is found to be contrary to commonly accepted community standards, is prohibited. This includes, without limitation, any information and material protected by copyright, trademark, trade secret, nondisclosure or confidentiality agreements, or other intellectual property rights, as well as any material that violates export control laws.
We, in our sole discretion and without notice, reserve the right, but undertake no duty, to review, edit, remove or delete any material submitted as a comment to a blog, forum or chat-room provided for display or placed on the Sites. Specifically, we reserve the right to delete or decline to post content that contains profanity; sexual content; overly graphic, disturbing or offensive material; vulgar or abusive language; hate speech, defamatory comments, or offensive language targeting any specific demographic; personal attacks of any kind; spam; or promotions for commercial products or services.
When you make a Submission, you grant Parker Waichman an unrestricted, irrevocable, perpetual, transferable, worldwide, royalty-free license to use, copy, reproduce, display, publish, publicly perform, transmit, and distribute the Submission, without compensation or accounting to you or anyone else. You represent and warrant that: (a) you have the right to submit the Submission to Parker Waichman and grant the licenses as described above; (b) Parker Waichman will not need to obtain licenses from any third party or pay royalties to any third party for its use of the Submission; (c) the Submission does not infringe any third party’s rights, including intellectual property rights and privacy rights; and (d) the Submission complies with these Terms of Use and all applicable laws and regulations.
By making a Submission, you agree that we are not responsible, and shall have no liability to you, with respect to any information or materials posted by others, including defamatory, offensive, or illicit material, even material that violates this “Terms of Use” agreement.
PRIVACY
Please review the Sites’s Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein and also governs your use of the Sites, to understand Parker Waichman’s privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy is accessible on our site’s home page.
SEPARATE AGREEMENTS
You may acquire products, services, and/or content from the Sites. We reserve the right to require that you agree to separate agreements as a condition of your use and/or purchase of such products, services, and/or content.
SEVERABILITY
If, for any reason any provision of these Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy, or any portion thereof, is declared invalid or unenforceable, such provision will be deemed modified to the extent necessary and possible to render it valid and enforceable, to the maximum extent permissible so as to give the intended effect thereof, and the remainder of these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy shall continue in full force and effect. In any event, the unenforceability or invalidity of any provision will not affect any other provision of these terms. These terms will continue in full force and effect and construed and enforced as if such provision had not been included, or had been modified, as provided above.
RESTRICTIONS ON USE
Subject to these “Terms of Use” and our “Privacy Policy,” the public areas of the Sites may be used for readers’ internal purposes. You agree not to:
reproduce, distribute, publicly display, or otherwise transfer the Sites;
adapt, alter, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble, or decompile the Sites;
prepare derivative works based on the Sites or any Parker Waichman technology;
remove, obscure, or modify any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices, marks or labels contained on or within the Sites;
frame, mirror, or in-line link the Sites, or incorporate into another website, application, or other service any Parker Waichman intellectual property;
use the Sites for any unlawful, fraudulent, or malicious purposes, or to solicit any such activity;
attempt to gain unauthorized access to any accounts, features, systems, or networks through hacking, password mining, or any other means;
interfere with any access control measures or attempt to disable or circumvent such security features;
post, transmit, submit, or include any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, sexually explicit, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable content, material, or information of any kind, or any content, material, or information that may give rise to criminal or civil liability;
submit or post any false or misleading information; and/or
violate, infringe, or misappropriate the intellectual property, publicity, privacy, or other proprietary rights of Parker Waichman, its licensors, or any other person or entity.
We reserve the right to prohibit access, use, conduct, communications, or content that we, in our sole discretion, deem to be harmful to the Sites, users, us, our brand, our business partners and licensors, or any other person or entity, or that violates these Terms of Use and/or applicable law.
Any unauthorized use automatically terminates the license granted to you hereunder. All rights not expressly granted in this “Terms of Use” agreement are reserved by us and our licensors.
Notification of Claimed Infringement:
Parker Waichman LLP
6 Harbor Park Drive
Port Washington, New York 11050
(516) 466-6500
WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS
EXCEPT AS MAY BE PROVIDED IN A SEPARATE WRITTEN AGREEMENT SIGNED BY THE PARTIES, THE SERVICES, CONTENT, AND/OR PRODUCTS ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS-IS”. WE, NOR ANY OF OUR LICENSORS, MAKE ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY WITH RESPECT TO SUCH PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND/OR CONTENT. EXCEPT AS MAY BE PROVIDED IN ANY SEPARATE WRITTEN AGREEMENT SIGNED BY THE PARTIES OR SEPARATE AGREEMENT ORIGINATING FROM THIS SITE, THIS SITE AND ITS LICENSORS SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, RELATING TO THIS SITE OR PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND/OR CONTENT ACQUIRED FROM THIS SITE INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, COMPLETENESS, TIMELINESS, CORRECTNESS, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THIS SITE AND ITS LICENSORS DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THIS SITE, ITS PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND/OR CONTENT: (A) WILL BE SECURE, TIMELY, UNINTERRUPTED, OR ERROR-FREE, OR OPERATE IN COMBINATION WITH ANY OTHER HARDWARE, SOFTWARE, SYSTEM, OR DATA; (B) WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS; OR (C) WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. WE DO NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE FOR ANY PURPOSE, INCLUDING ANY MEDICAL ADVICE REGARDING ANY ASPECT OF YOUR PARTICIPATION IN A FITNESS PROGRAM. ALL INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THIS SITE IS FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. THESE DISCLAIMERS CONSTITUTE AN ESSENTIAL PART OF THIS AGREEMENT. NO PURCHASE OR USE OF THE ITEMS OFFERED BY THIS SITE IS AUTHORIZED HEREUNDER EXCEPT UNDER THESE DISCLAIMERS. IF IMPLIED WARRANTIES MAY NOT BE DISCLAIMED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, THEN ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARE LIMITED IN DURATION TO THE PERIOD REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW. SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY MAY LAST, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Contact Form
FREE CASE EVALUATION
Fill out this form for FREE,Immediate, Case Evaluation
Ngage
Why Have So Many Contacted Us?
I would like to take this opportunity to thank you and all the lawyers involved at your firm who worked diligently and tirelessly to bring about the positive result in my case. I will continue to keep your firm uppermost in mind as the need arises for legal counsel for me, members of my...
~ Elizabeth D. Parker Waichman was there for my family when one of our family members was desperately in need of assistance. We will be forever grateful to all for the help they provided.
~ Ivy F. Everyone I have dealt with at your firm has been very professional and courteous. My phone calls were always returned quickly and all of my questions were answered in a thorough manner. Mr. Zekowski is always on top of his game. He is very knowledgeable about the law and extremely professional.
~ Syndee K.
VIEW MORE REVIEWS
LEAVE A REVIEW
How Can We Help You?
Fill out the form below to receive a free confidential consultation.
New York
Parker Waichman LLP
59 Maiden Lane, 6th Floor
New York,
NY
10038
(212) 267-6700
$10,000+
Brooklyn
Parker Waichman LLP
300 Cadman Plaza West
One Pierrepont Plaza, 12th Floor
HomeAbout Us
Our Attorneys & StaffParker Waichman All BiosWhy Trust Us? Back
Locations
Bronx Personal Injury AttorneysBrookly AttorneysFlorida AttorneysLong Island AttorneysNew Jersey AttorneysNew York AttorneysQueens Attorneys Back
Our Results
Client ReviewsVerdicts & Settlements Back
Practice Areas
Accidents
Bicycle, Scooter, and Electric Bike AccidentCar Accident LawyersMotorcycle Accident LawyersPain and Suffering LawyerPedestrian Accident AttorneysTruck Accident Lawyers Back
CoronavirusComplex Litigation
Business LitigationsClass ActionsConsumer FraudDefective DrugsDefective Medical DevicesFracking LawsuitsMore Complex Litigation LawsuitsOvertime Law/WagesToxic TortsWhistleblowers Back
Intentional Acts
Bullying / Cyber BullyingMandalay Bay MassacreWorkplace Violence Back
Medical Malpractice
Cerebral Palsy Malpractice Injury LawsuitsStevens Johnson Syndrome (SJS) Disease Injury Back
Police Misconduct & Brutality LawyersProduct LiabilitySex Abuse
Boy Scouts Sexual Abuse LawyersClergy Abuse LawyersDr Reginald Archibald Sex AbuseSex Abuse Civil Statute of LimitationsState Child Victims Act (New York) Back
Negligence
Birth Injury Lawsuit LawyersFire and Burn Injury LawyersTraumatic Brain Injury LawyersWrongful Death Lawyers Back
Nursing Home AbusePremises Liability
Balcony Railing FailureConstruction Accident LawyersCrowd ManagementHotel SecurityLabor Law Injury LawyersSlip and Fall Injury Attorneys Back
Workers’ Comp & COVID-19 AttorneysZadroga 911 Lawyers
911 ClaimsWorld Trade Center Health ProgramWorld Trade Center Health ProgramWTC Health Program Covered ConditionsWTC VCF Back
Back
Defective Drugs
ElmironNexiumNSAID AttorneysPrevacidPrilosecProtonixProton Pump Inhibitors (PPI)Tasigna LawyersTruvada LawsuitUloricVaccine Injury LawyersXeljanzZantac Back
Defective Medical Devices
Bair Hugger BlanketsDePuy Pinnacle HipEthicon Physio Hernia MeshHernia MeshHip ReplacementSt. Jude DefibrillatorSurgical Staples Back
Defective Products
3M Earplugs Hearing LossBreast Implant LymphomaHip Replacement LawsuitsJuul & E-CigarettesLithium-Ion BatteriesTalcum Powder Back
Resources
Online ResourcesPW BrochureStatutes Of LimitationVideo Vault Back
FAQsBreaking NewsContact Us
× Close Panel
